htmlhelpcentral.com 2003-10-08

# HTML Help Central - Privacy Policy

**HTML Help Central Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement covers www.htmlhelpcentral.com and all of its properties and subsidiaries. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices to our users. HTML Help Central is the sole owner of all information collected from our site. 

Our server automatically logs information about our visitors, including but not limited to IP address, the page(s) they visited, their HTTP referrer, their browser and version, age groups, geographic location, the duration of their visit, etc. All information that is not personally identifiable is aggregated to present demographic data to advertisers. 

Additionally, we use a third party advertising firm to serve some ads on our site. This third party collects information that is not personally identifiable regarding our visitors. This data is used to better suit ad content for each individual viewer. 

Additionally, users are required to register to use our message board software. During registration, users are required to provide certain information, including an email address and a password. This information is never sold to any third party. Any information we aggregate for presentation to advertisers is not personally identifiable, and your anonymity will be protected. Other information that is not personally identifiable such as age group, geographic location, etc. may be aggregated for presentation to advertisers. Passwords for use with our message board software are encrypted in our database. No one can get them, no one can decipher them. “Personal Messages” or “Private Message” sent and received using our message board software should not be considered as private. Authorized message board administrators have complete access to them for moderation purposes. “Private messages” and “Personal messages” are subject to the same rules and regulations that govern the public areas of the message boards.

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, when registering to use the message board, users can choose not to receive email from authorized message board moderators and administrators by choosing "no" for the "Allow Bulletin Board Administrators and Moderators To Send You Email Notices?" option in the user control panel. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing privacy@htmlhelpcentral.com with “unsubscribe” in the subject line. We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the message board's user control panel to opt-out of mailings.

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, HTML Help Central, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ accounts or personally identifiable information. This can be done at the by emailing privacy@htmlhelpcentral.com.
